Children’s Network of Solano County Privacy Policy

Our Commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining

our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information

is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage

and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. Our privacy

policy is designed to inform you of the types of information we collect, how we use that

information, and the circumstances under which we will share it with nonaffiliated third parties.

Information Collection and Use

The Children's Network of Solano County is the sole owner of the information collected on this

site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways differently than we have

disclosed in this statement. The Children's Network of Solano County collects information from

our users at several different points on our website.

Examples of the types of nonpublic personal information collected at these pages are:

• Name

• Address

• Web address

• Email address

• Phone Number

Additionally, we collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources (in

addition to our website):

• Information we receive from you on applications or other forms

• Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates and others

Categories of Nonaffiliated Third Parties to Whom we May Disclose Nonpublic Personal

Information

Nonaffiliated third parties are those companies not under direct or indirect ownership or control

with The Children's Network of Solano County. We only disclose personal information about you

to the following types of nonaffiliated third parties: mailing houses that prepare and send

newsletters, postcards and other information to you on our behalf.

Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user.

Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.

Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates

Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather

broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally

identifiable information.

Sharing

We partner with other parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these

services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party

to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use use nonpublic personally

identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. We do not otherwise

disclose nonpublic information to anyone, except as permitted by law.

Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, The Children's Network of

Solano County are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage

our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and

every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies

solely to information collected by this Web site. Operators may be subject to the FTC's privacy

regulations and if so, (i) the FTC's regulations contain sample disclosures that operators may

consider; and (ii) operators may be required to send annual notices in addition to initial

disclosures to their customers.

Security

This website takes precautions to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive

information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. Only

employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a

customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our

employees use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they

return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore,

ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well

as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the

importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is

protected.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to

childnet@childnet.org.

Correction/Updating Personal Information

If a user’s nonpublic personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a

user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or

remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done by calling our

headquarters at 707-421-7229 or by emailing our Customer Support Department at

childnet@childnet.org for more instructions.

Opt-out requirements

As provided in this policy, we only provide your nonpublic personal information to a nonaffiliated

third party in conjunction with the services that you have requested that we provide to you. All

nonaffiliated third parties to whom we disclose your nonpublic personal information are

contractually prohibited by us to disclose or use the information other than to carry out the

transactions that you have requested. Accordingly, there is nothing for a user to opt out of with

respect to how we currently use their non-public personal information.

Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our

users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances,

if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a

manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an

email or US mailing so as to enable users to "opt-out" if we use their information in this different

manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the

information was collected.
